http://www.tryingtoconceive.com/privacy-policy

Information Collection and Use
While using TryingToConceive.com (hereafter referred to as "site"), you may be asked to provide with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name, phone number, and address and we will do our best to keep that information private.
Log Data
We want to inform you that whenever you visit our site, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, pages  that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.
Our website uses these “cookies” to collect information and to improve what we provide. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our site.
Security
We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Links to Other Sites
Our site may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites, read more. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our site does not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
Email us if you have a question!
Categories
TTC Store
Protect Early Pregnancy
Abbreviations
Annoying Comments
Ask Mama Kath
BBT Charts
Clomid Club
Egg Whites
PCOS
Pelvic Girdle (Psoas)
Successes & Symptoms
Video Library
Acid vs. Alkaline
Subscribe for TTC Tips
*
Required
First name *
Email Address *
Home Phone Number
Talk to me!
Prove you're not a robot *
Subscribe to: Newsletter
Next
Prev
Increase Fertility
{module_webapps,21964,a}
©Trying to Conceive, Mama Kath (Momma Kath), Herbs for Her & Him 1998-2020 | ©FertilEDGE 2014-2020
All Rights Reserved. Natural Products & Information to Conceive Naturally.
*PLEASE NOTE: The information provided on this site is intended to serve only as a supplement to your resources and is in no way to be considered medical advice, medical diagnosis or treatment. Always check with your obstetrician, physician, midwife, or other health care provider before choosing to do or not do any course of action.
___________________________________________________________
Shopping cart is empty.
